# Nithin R

Experienced Process Associate with over 2 +years of experience in Aggregate Intelligence. Identified and resolved process issues to drive optimal workflow and business growth. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction. Seasoned in coordinating and implementing business process improvement projects while enhancing effectiveness and efficiency in support of business goals.



### **Employment History**

# Process Associate at Aggregate Intelligence, Coimbatore OCTOBER 2021 – PRESENT

Worked with SQL servers, Solving issue in process based on projects, Testing python scripts on AWS machines. Developed efficient improvement plans in alignment with goals and specification. Identified and resolved process issues to drive optimal workflow and business growth.

## Process Associate (SQL) at Aggregate Intelligence, Coimbatore

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

#### **SQL Server Troubleshooting:**

- \* Expertise in Microsoft SQL Server performance tuning.
- \* Proficient in resolving CPU and memory utilization issues.
- \* Skilled in query optimization, indexing, and handling database deadlocks.
- \* Familiar with SQL Profile and SQL Server Management Studio (SSMS) for efficient database management.

# AWS cloud partitioner knowledgeable at Aggregate Intelligence, Coimbatore

JUNE 2023 - SEPTEMBER 2023

#### **AWS Cloud Management:**

- \* Proficient in AWS EC2 instance provisioning and monitoring.
- \* Skilled in using Auto Scaling and CloudWatch for resource optimization.
- \* Experience with launching and managing E2 instances for various workloads.
- \* Launching in different instance type.

#### Python basic knowledge:

- · Python oops concept
- File handling
- Python MYSQL
- · Python MongoDB
- · File handling

#### Details

Coimbatore, India 9344972308 nm12022000@gmail.com

#### Links

<u>linkedin</u> <u>GitHub</u> <u>Project Link</u>

#### Skills

MS Word

AWS cloud partitioner

SQL knowledge,

MS Excel,

Technical Skills

Python (Udemy certificate)

Full stack development with python

HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP

**JavaScript** 

REACTJS

Tailwind CSS

Languages



#### Education

B.Sc[IT] at Kathir college of arts and science, Coimbatore
JUNE 2018 – JULY 2021

PERCENTAGE OFMARKS(%) 60 at B.Sc[IT], Coimbatore
JANUARY 2018 – JANUARY 2021

HSC at Annai velankanni matyriculation higher secondary school, Coimbatore

MARCH 2018

### **Project**

Front-end project, Coimbatore

Completely responsive Events webpage in working condition to the client.

Project Link: https://nithinr12.github.io/MissionKGT/

**Grocery store project** 

It is ongoing project. End to end user experience project.

### **Certified Course**

Python (Basic)

SEPTEMBER 2023 - OCTOBER 2023



